# 哈喽 大家好
Hello everyone
# 前几天买了一个猪
We bought a pig a few days ago
# 因为要吃烤全猪
as we want to have a whole BBQ pig
# 现在所以我来准备焊一个架子
So now I'm going to make a rack
# 烤架
A grilling rack
# 这次要烤真正的烤全猪
This time we are going to grill a real whole BBQ pig
# 是不是 四伯爷
Is that right, uncle?
# 你说野猪撒
You have to say "wild pig"
# 烤全猪 什么名称你都
"Whole BBQ pig"? You can't even make the name...
# 不搞定
...make an accurate name
# 四伯爷这里帮我弄上去哈
Uncle, could you help me fix it?
# 好
Good
# 弄斜点嘛还是弄正点哦
Should it be slanted or straight?
# 斜点嘎
Slanted, right?
# 再斜点都不关事
It can be even more slanted
# 再斜点才登得起力点是个三角形都嘛
It must be more slanted to support more weight. You know, triangle
# 好嘛
OK
# 对
Good
# 不慌不慌
Easy, easy
# 这哈踩到那里
Fix that part
# 好
Good
# 点着根 这根点了再反转来一哈就搞了
Weld this part. Weld it, and then we just need to flip it and do it again
# 看嘛 这里一敲都掉了
Watch here. This part can be knocked apart
# 那里哦
Which part?
# 来 再焊它哈
Alright, weld it again
# 要是那种焊航空母舰的像你这样焊起焊疤的话
If an aircraft carrier has such kind of weld like you did
# 搞不好下海就进水沉了
it's probably going to sink immediately after launch
# 这里 还有这里 每个都再焊一下
Here, and here. Weld both places
# 好
OK
# 搭错了
You built it wrong
# 你搭再那里去了
How do you want to build it?
# 都得行
Whatever
# 只要搭在铁上都得行
It works as long as it touches iron
# 这根你要挨着撒
These two parts should be in touch
# 不挨到你试一下嘛
Doesn't matter. You can try
# 啊
Huh?
# 搭在铁上都没得事得
It works as long as it touches some iron
# 是啊
Yeah
# 不得行 通不到电
Doesn't work. Electricity doesn't flow through
# 这样子差不多
This way should work
# 对了
Yeah
# 90厘米
90 centimeters
# 90
# 要得 好
Alright, good
# 可以了
Finished
# 放不下去
Hehe, can't put it down
# 那边再敲哈
Try knocking that part
# 放不下去到时候这个重新摆哈就是
Can't put it down. We can just lay the bricks again
# 来 取出来
Come on, let's take it out
# 这个砖可以重新摆的
We can lay the bricks again
# 哦噢 这样子还可以
Wow, looks great
# 把它抬起来再放下去
We can lift it and then drop it
# 它都挡不到
And nothing is blocked
# 到时候猪儿就放在上面烤
Then we can put the pig here and grill
# 这个碳堆到这个位置
The charcoal is at this position
# 这里的一片全部弄来铺碳
This whole area will be charcoal
# 然后砖直接垫在这里就是
And we can simply lay the bricks at the bottom
# 都不用砌这种得了
We don't even need to build such stoves
# 就明天烤嘛 明天不落雨
It's grill it tomorrow. It doesn't rain tomorrow
# 要得嘛 要得嘛 明天就早点干嘛
Sure, sure. Let's do it early tomorrow
# 要得 把它抬进去
Sure. Let's move it inside
# 好
Alright
# 我们为了吃这个猪真的是下了很多功夫了
We've really made great effort to eat that pig
# 还是放在那里
Put it over there?
# 慢点哦
Careful
# 我又不关事
Doesn't matter to me